Abishek Kanageswaran

SKILLS

HTML/CSS(SCSS)
Figma (Designing)
JavaScript (ES6+, jQuery)
React JS (Redux)
Firebase
Git

EDUCATION

Franklin University B.S. in Web Development GPA 3.0 + April 2016 - May 2021 Columbus, OH

CONTACT

Abishekkanageswaran70@gmail.com

in http://www.linkedin.com/in/abishek1718

((614) – 701 – 8131

https://www.Abishek.fyi

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Front End Developer with a passion for website development and success in managing development projects. Experienced in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React JS. Proficient in translating UI/UX design wireframes to actual code, creating user interfaces, and integrating front-end aspects of application while ensuring maximum stability.

EXPERIENCE

Franklin University

Student Registrar Assistant - March 2018 - Present, Ohio (3 years +)

- Responsible for providing support to the Registrar Department procedures, such as Scanning official transcripts/Document into the system.
- Managed and organized student transcripts for transferring students to ensure all transcripts are accurate.
- Record transfer credit, advance placement and grade changes.
- Maintain accurate student records to compliance regulation.

Franklin University

Circulation team assistant - April 2017 to March 2018

- Responsible for providing support to the Circulation Department procedures, such as checking in and checking out materials.
- Excellent customer service skills to provide library services to patrons, staff, and faculty.
- Monitor Circulation email, Manage the library room reservations, Troubleshoot computer, copier, and other library equipment issues. Manage shelf reading and shelf care, Oversee the accurate shelving of library material, Maintain Circulation Desk statistics.

PROJECTS

Fair Lanka (https://www.fairlanka.info)

- Built a website for a wholesale & Retail company from scratch.
- Display Information about the business model, what company offers, Hours of operation and a contact form for more discussion.
- Tools Used: HTML/CSS, React JS & Netlify

Movie Database App (https://zen-einstein-67ea59.netlify.app/)

- Build a Movie Database App like IMDb Website.
- Display recent movies, story line, ratings & search for favorite movies.
- Tools Used: HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.